<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>DataTime</title>
        <link>https://dtalg.com/</link>
        <description>DataTime</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>liuhanmeng@westlake.edu.cn (Bimu)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>liuhanmeng@westlake.edu.cn (Bimu)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 23:46:09 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://dtalg.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Article 1</title>
    <link>https://dtalg.com/article-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 23:46:09 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://dtalg.com/article-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A A/B testing A statistical way of comparing two (or more) techniques, typically an incumbent against a new rival. A/B testing aims to determine not only which technique performs better but also to understand whether the difference is statistically significant. A/B testing usually considers only two techniques using one measurement, but it can be applied to any finite number of techniques and measures.
accuracy The fraction of predictions that a classification model got right.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Did auto correction saved Apple? if it is not for this technology , there won&#39;t be the first gen iPhone</title>
    <link>https://dtalg.com/video-2/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 12:10:01 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://dtalg.com/video-2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[First gen iPhone" First gen iPhone  In 2007, Apple launched the first generation of iPhone, equipped with a 3.5 inch display, there is only one home button in the front, the compact size of the phone let it easily sit on the palm of your hand. Customers worldwide are crazy about this new design. While before that, it is this revolutional form of factory, that almost killed the unrevealed project.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>DataTime logo reveal</title>
    <link>https://dtalg.com/video-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:37:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://dtalg.com/video-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[   ]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Landscape of Lijiang Yunnan</title>
    <link>https://dtalg.com/photo-1/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:18:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://dtalg.com/photo-1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Wetland" Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Wetland  Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Lake" Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Lake  Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Trees and Wind" Lashihai Wetland Natural Park, Lijiang, Yunnan Trees and Wind  Jade Dragon Snow Mountain, Lijiang, Yunnan Snow mountain" Jade Dragon Snow Mountain, Lijiang, Yunnan Snow mountain  Yuhu Villege, Lijiang, Yunnan Old Woman"]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
